+1000 for Cargo Cult Programming. When combined with the H1B issue you get Coolies to lift your Cargo too! :-)
All telepaths are on vacation now - can you show some code ?
Hello nobody cares about your life story :) get to the point
phewwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwww. I wish sarcasm was more apparent in text format.
Clearly he hasn't answered it by your comments below you're simply wasting people's time by being to stubborn to provide any reasonable information.
[links](https://www.google.com/webhp?sourceid=chrome-instant&rlz=1C1LEND_enUS445US445&ion=1&espv=2&ie=UTF-8#q=create+time+limited+trial+java+program)
did you really asked this question?
Really? You don't know about String.Substring ?
If i would've done that i wouldn't be asking here. The thing is i don't know how to approach to get the desired result.
Those who care IE is fucking dumb developers. :) just sayin' :D
Are you sure that you understand VBA properly?   In the code Find returns :
you can show pdf in your app without calling another application so why do you want to open other application.
i´d start by reading through a basic java tutorial...
Sucks to be you.
fuck fuck fuck fuck
fuck fuck fuck fuck fukc
POST YOUR CODE.. WE ARE NOT CLAIRVOYANT.
Blah blah blah blah...
Get the f**** o** from here. this is not portal site.
[why my question is getting downvotes](http://meta.stackoverflow.com/questions/252677/when-is-it-justifiable-to-downvote-a-question)
oh thank you for opening my eyes on this amusing fact!
Stop cheating. You're not going to get that job.
that would never work
Ok who the hell are you to edit my stuff
All I need is this code fixed or at least some help if you're not going to get the hell off my question and go to the next one
And **** about the Google search may be you need to use this link : https://goo.gl/GzjTG6
if you can't help don't tell shit
That's called a `UITextView`.
Oh ya zébbii ...
Duplicating existing already linked answers and calling people names is what's not constructive. I think it just makes it clear what you're going for in these answers.
without any explanation & what the user is using is not mentioned so can you please justify this answer ?
hire a developer. stackoverflow is not a place to get your work done for free.
So is a pencil  paper envelope and stamp an alternative
Wrong. You don't understand Spring. Did you even read my answer?
Really you can't understand the error statement?
if you cant help ..atleast dont piss off anyone..idiot...
I'm flagging this question to be closed as too broad because it is merely a Gimme the codez question the likes of which are not welcome or encouraged on Stackoverflow.
nice copy of mine and **** styles :)
I found what you're asking in the documentation of Localytics in less than 2 minutes... Did you even bother to look ???
`(laziness stupidity... ` Well aren't you just an arrogant arse.
Too dumb long read?
when someone don't have answer he tried to degrade and get points.
Gentleman i think you miss understand what I am trying to do.
Stop trolling and get a job.
Fart sound. not free
just answer the question
Try not to be helpless type default.rd.xml in the Google query box.
Why are people being cunts? Voting me down. I said I was a newb. Tossers.Thanks for the feedback.
I've helped loads of people over the years even when a question wasn't perfect. People on here are 'question fascists'. The site attracts assholes.
Oh really? It turns out I tried that and it didn't work! Do you think I'd post a question on here without trying to refresh the session?
An array is not a pointer and vice-versa. And please RTFM. See the `printf` manpage.
you need to move the whole title part to the top of the loop.. come on common sense
Thanks for being a published asshole
Sorry forgot to say - a Jerk also
Down-voting your answer until the property update behaviour gets sorted out. Will undo the vote once we clarify this matter.
That's why I am asking. If you don't know the answer then be quiet.
_italic_ usually sucks
Yes go ahead and delete it and don't ask such questions here again.
*I know PHP Storm is built on Eclipse* Yeah right. That explains a lot!
Top SO Google result filled with useful information closed by some fuckwit moderator who probably doesn't even know what XML is. Gooooo SO!
ne pas être intelligent
What exactly are you doing here? This program reads like someone spliced random lines from some very strange spanish c program together.
une personne stupide essaie d'être intelligent si je l'ai fait .
hell to your comment idiot.
hell to your Zend certifications RASCAL
sorry forum nazi
this is wrong . your solution will create a list from [5  num+4]
Fraction is not the same as remainder. But maybe that techno-speak is too  complicated. Too bad programming is a techno-thingy.
Have you *tried* to do it with streams? Don't just expect Stack-Overflow users to refactor your code for you...
WHO THE FUCK DOWNVOTED?????
Finally answer that makes sense I got bored -1-ing every other attempt to answer this one.
So what if it worked perfectly before? They changed something in their vendor build of android and perhaps it doesn't work now until they patch it... ?
I voted as too broad did not vote dup.  Not much point in bitching at the only person that is trying to help you.  Focus on your object design problem to get somewhere.
Hey **** are you always such a pedantic c.u.nt? Why don't you go f.u.ck. yourself you pseudo-intellectual elitist b.it.c.h
What the actual fuck can you just please help me. I tried a lot of others forums. Seems this one could be my savior.
Well I don't want to use the letter i in my code. How can I declare main?
Why even use DateTime if you're going to still use date and strtotime? Get rid of them and clean this up.
I fart in your general direction!
This is a genuinely terrible answer which you should be ashamed of giving. Don't answer this kind of question again.
The answer couldn't be simpler. You are of course using Unity's UI right? Simply look at the `.text` property of the `Button` and of course you have your answer.
WTF vote to close. Point me in the right direction.
He didn't ask for your opinion; the timing depends on the receiver; and you haven't addressed the major fallacy in his question.
Professional developers hate him!
MongoDB is 'awesome' is a pretty terrible answer. Furthermore your lack of experience with Cassandra does not qualify you to answer this question.
Are you retarded or what? If the problem is not in your table you should put the fucking code where you do the insert.
Do you know what templates are and how they are spelled? What exactly is the problem?
who downvoted me ?idiots
RTFM? https://msdn.microsoft.com/en-CA/library/ms177677.aspx
Please don't badger me with rules.  I only made a stackoverflow account for this one question because I've tried for literally about 2 months and nothing works.
yeah i'm about to turn 13 next week. you got beef son?
It's essentially the same code you use to exclude all questions that don't show what you've tried.
This is not a code translation service. There are no [tag:c++] scripts. What is this for? If it's a commercial project I could help you if you pay.
If you can't answer the question you're useless keep it moving. If a moderator wants to edit anything he/she can I don't have to an intelligent person will understand.
What in the heck does this answer have anything to do with the question?
well you can't tell me what to do so suck my balls
English probably
all the forms input always should be inside the form tag don't you know that??
The idiot who downvoted obviously didn't read the bold marked text *rolls eyes*
**He always brings the same information** who is this?? And unclear your question !!
how about you stop munching curry?
Oh! Yes. Don't relieve it to anybody. Eat yourself.
That's a pretty arrogant statement don't you think. Perhaps Stack Overflow is not the best place for you.
IT WORKS!!! THERE IS NO COUNTER STATEMENT SECONDLY IF I PUT != IT DOESNT DO ANYTHING THUS IT WORKS LISTEN BEFORE YOU SPEAK
Step 1: Go to school and get a CS degree
First of all you need to learn the human language to understand the What topics can I ask about here? help site of Stack Overflow.
asked the moderator to move it and got downvoted. This is some shit.
Links can die post the actual *relevant* code here
You're dumb don't write me anymore
Fuck off the code works
Okay special snowflake. Yes I only downvoted you because I'm too stupid to write code as awesome as yours.
have you even thought to look at the JavaDoc for `AtomicInteger `?
Although I appreciate you pointing me towards a great resource. I was hoping to actually receive a response like hey in cases like these i.... so honestly. Screw you.
I have sovled this problemthe same as you said netstat -abn.
what a fuckIt does not listen localhost:80and can't access itsef by domain name.
Thank you captain obvious! ;-)
You are really an idiot.  Now I see you down voted my other question.  Get a life.
**Read** the question...
You don't seem to understand what the word *override* means.  Try a dictionary please read it carefully.
Hey smart guy even so you stopped for looking and lose time answering it get a life nerd
Please show code.  The OP asks for code.
use a bloody search engine!!!!
Also which muppet upvoted?
So you don't really understand any of this code?
You don't need to say that buddy. If you can't help then Fish off and stop acting like you are the CEO of Stack Overflow lol.
I HAVE NOT GIVEN ANY CONNECTION STRING ITS CODE FIRST TO NEW DB DEPLOYMENT SO BY DEFAULT ON MY PC IT IS **creating** database but on client pc not creating
You should read a manual first.
You know what else you can do? You can go **c* yourself. You fill in the letters and let me know if that violates something else.
wtf this is off topic?
how is it off topic wtf
Javascript people don't give importance to archtecture subjects unfortunatelly. It's different from Java people.
fuck you i can swear as much as i want you cunt btw thanks
it's very good idea to harash new people that trying to enter your world thank you a lot... i am trying to understand sth but as i see u are not supposed to help me...
We provide a service of reading error messages for people too busy to read them.
Why don't you try it instead of letting us debug your code. Or better - search first
Sorry but I have to say you have no clue what you're doing. Your code is full of nonsenses. Throw it and learn how to program first.
Only ignorant people can downvote a question without any explanation in comments
I love how you call the bullshit American time normal.
I run a Seattle Website Development firm is this your standard business practice outsource your work to Stack Overflow?
done that already... I'm not here to waste time...
That is kind of nonsense. The user needs to authenticate silently without having to enter a username or password I guess ?
use a search engine?
SO is not a code writing service.
Sorry again I fucked up badly. I corrected it again.
If my solution had a simple error there would have been barrage of downvotes.
true ... though better make sure you know the rules of what kind of questions to ask around there ...
if you cannot differenciate then better dont comment
if you can't look at an algorithm for 1hour to find out what it does then you should probably quit being a programmer....
That is much ABC worpdress I know all that already in which none can achieve my needs.
yes but OP says it doesn't make any difference so you might wanna remove this as an answer.
I hear google can find all kinds of things or so I've been told
**** get a life! And don't ever answer to any questions that you don't have anything to give. You are a smartass without and only waste this Web site's topis.
While I agree that you are still learning to post good questions why do the rest of us have to suffer?
Jesus. This is supposed to be an interactive community. I could care less about formatting I want to ask other coders for some advice. That shouldn't be a problem.
oh and if you're trying to be cute your account could be banned. So think a little.
You weren't sad. You deleted my email accounts and screwed over my team. Go fuck yourself.
I think **** downvote me cause i downvote him :D
Please add some more info about what you are getting. Shame you got a downvote without a chance to edit it first. Cheers
I think this is the most edited answer today. You should gain a badge lol..
What does It doesn't work mean?! FFS You get an exception? The world ends?
OR operator is `||` not `or`
ITS FUCKING WORKING!
 I think you need something better to do.
Please start by reading a Python tutorial. Your code isn't even close to valid Python.
Fuck off. Idiot.
Mother fuckers like you are destroying SO.
Is your mom off topic too?
You can get a path like c:\one\two/three ... And it fucks shit up.
not working you canst it here: https://regex101.com/
This is not the place to get your homework done. At least convert that text to ASCII rather than posting a picture. Lazy bone.
Actually my code is perfectly formatted.  Two other people were able to tell what I was asking so stop bitching.
ill put you on hold
Thanks I got the answer on my own. If you know employee schema you should have got my question.
can you give any successful code.........because I don't have any idea about this...I read the documentation but is not enough for fresher
Doesn't meet *your* imaginary specifications and wrong are two separate things.
yep you go it.bright guy
Oh...... What stupid a question! I'm sorry to waste you time ...
Offtopic: This is ridiculous. I hit Submit and in less than 5 seconds a -1 vote is here. You cannot even have read the whole question.
When you even don't know that selenium webdriver can handle the file upload then please keep silent ..
Before giving minus points please read properly or ask what I am asking for
Bullshit answer. how this even selected as answer?
What have you tried to solve your problem? Have you tried to print any string with that 'format' function?
As it stands this question is too broad.  Do you have a more specific programming question?
You're not even using ARC? Really?
Links rot. You don't know that?
So you found the solution by yourself just after reading it on my answer. Fair play to you.
did it take a lot of research to count the sides of the +?
Edited...  Please don't make me regret answering this.
Seriously useless morons I didn't ask for an opinion. This site has gone to the dogs f u.
Only a stupid developer would do that.
Perhaps you could start by learning Python's base types before asking the obvious ?
As per my guess those who cleared mongo university course very well know about **[$unwind](https://docs.mongodb.org/manual/reference/operator/aggregation/unwind/)**
I think is clear enough.... I think i explained clearly enough what i have allready try. if you cannot help just leave...
3 dislikes wtf guys  this community is slowly moving to asshole level 9001
fuck this shit why i am even bothering i will write my own generator -.-
Possibly but does it matter.  You recently duped one of my answers that didn't have any relevance to the duped one.
_Please help! I am not good in regex related things._ you don't need RegEx. Use `indexOf`.
Thats OK Take your time We have nothing better to do.... Oh! Yes we do!! Moving on.
Why would you take an assignment if you don't know how to do it?
***who gave me -1 is one cannot understand the question if you find yourself one of them please leave my question now!***