Of course it's code you insensitive clod!
If you think you're being clever you aren't.
Mexican police takes a random african animal and pour soda with chili into its nose until it admits that it's an elephant.
Pure science? WTF does that mean? You think NaCl doesn't come in a 1:1 relationship?
Seriously? Did you even bother to look at the documentation for UIButton?
Just remember that they hate you
I like the obfuscation in your answer text.  Makes it very hard to read.  Ever heard of the Enter key?
You must live in a box then.
Yeah im a baby give it to me in a bottle lol.
I think we've reached a new low of laziness.
They are proud of it but sometimes it becomes pain in the ass.
Your answer on the other hand is worthless.
the curly quotes fsck with the code parsing
Your syntax is junk
I second the beatings.
Let me guess are you a perl programmer?
Don't waste your time trying to make this work it isn't worth it.
Agree but -1 for answering a dupe.  You should know better.
Because is mildly insane.  `espresso-mode` is the Javascript mode for sane people.
-1 useless answer
Works on my machine.  Somebody is blocking you.  Are you Chinese?
This is pretty fec-ked up.  
Why on Earth would you want to imitate something this butt-ugly?
I would upvote this answer but I just hate this oh downvote me you senseless clods bullshit.  Especially repeated twice.
shut up sir.....
I'm looking for a Klein bottle with some wine in it. Any suggestions?
Its called your brain. If you can't competently review code ask someone else to do it.
ANYONE??? HELLOOOO???
I believe you've learned that in your school.
goddamnit Novice is not the word
Your professor's a retard.  Not that strange really.
Haha what a retard yeah if I tried to build then I would have realized that :)
Stupid solution he's don't need that
Do not clone my post
Maybe b/c people like you that don't make useful feedback are the reason...
Everyone who thinks he can wiggle around writing a real parser by applying regex instead needs his nose wiped in the shit this inevitably ends in.
With a reputation > 7000 you might know where the Python documentation is.
there is no need of downvote. huh wht to do with this kind of people.
if you dont want to answers.. just.. dont answer!
There is no programming question here.  You have an invalid entry in your file.
omfg what is that?
Is this a troll?
look can you please stop posting such unrelated rubbish.
-1: Admittedly iphone camera on google doesn't give you any useful links but spend an extra 30 seconds and google for iphone camera tutorial and you're done.
Okay this one gets my funniest post of the day.  :)
shut up............
That means that you have fucked-up the routes. Come on new question!
This shows remarkably little effort.
Wow what a terrible mess.
Its the number of fucks will not reduce the gestation period
`sql-server` AND `oracle` tags? And an explanation as well? It's homework isn't it?
If somebody asked me that question I would want to punch them in the face. And then answer Apples and oranges
+1 Good answer to a poor question.
man this is a programming forum not trig.
wtf? how is this a real question?
Have you bothered to actually look at the PHP docs and see how to do it or do you just want somebody to spoonfeed you the codez
blog post my foot.
And maybe taking a class on databases. Or even just reading all the way through a tutorial.
This shows zero effort on the author's part.
wow now that is lazy... I can't believe people are actually willing to help you? :S
you improbably thorough m*****f****r.
Cant believe those Aholes -1 repped me
You should really learn the basics of web-programming before creating a web page if you don't even know the difference between client-side and server-side script languages.
Is this homework?
hypercrypt it is a client's requirement.Client is female and she hates all the URL and website address stuff. :)
Wow didn't know you can convert HTML tables into Excel files...
He likes to ask questions
If API documents are hard for you to read then you should *learn* how to read them first.
And the award goes to the Asp.net team for most retarded class name...
Read the documentation -- **** is correct and the documentation will tell you how to do this.
RTFM or ask a new question.
witch! burn him!!
Yeah. Post the real error.
Do you have any objective-c programming experience?
lack of research effort
Take your other questions you asked and mark the answers you think is right.
my eyes!!!!.............
Read a C++ book.
Don't post question for silly mistakes. You actually wrote the code to get the text from the edittext in the oncreate() itself.
You're an idiot.
R u crazy ****??I will give you -1 for this stupid answer.I am not asking for this.Please read my question carefully...
a ton of research eh ? this is the second hit on google: http://www.braemoor.co.uk/software/postcodes.shtml
Downvoters don't have a cow... what do you want?  Sometimes you just want to take the first item from a dictionary whatever that item happens to be.
Did you consider reading the documentation?
The answer links to the docs what more would you want?
Why do you even care?
nut-searing pain - couldn't have said it better.
WTH? TIA? This Is Awkward? Typical Ignorant American?
I don't think this is even worth asking.. a small google search would of given you the answer.. or just stick with trial and error and experimenting.
ever try google?
sorry can't help myself:  reputation: 1
We don't magical stick and ball to understand your word. Post code
Try to switch on the thing between ya ears before spamming and make people waste their time.
I don't know wtf does async.whilst() and I don't care.
can u figure out how to do this stupid crap?
Ask all those people who you've always heard this from.
It was the first result on the exact title as mentioned in the comment. Now it isn't. The first hit is now tragically this stupid question.
So what's the question? What's the code? Or do you prefer us to provide you with magic out of the air?
i post same thing..bt ur confused again?
I have already done that if you look at my code at the top invoking the ggplot. did you notice the + theme() + ???
What a crazy idea to close this question! Jesus holy Chirst!
Bloody fool people don't try to give down vote without knowing the answers.. Give Down vote with justification.
This question shows zero research effort...
just wtf... closevote
Thanks for time wasting.
lame shit. i simply want to assign multiple error callbacks when a $http.get throws an error.
How to delete this question?
Maybe should read about Accessing array values?
Google is a hell of a drug.
Or check the source. You know since it's open source.
you have to read. the problem is a link to the picture of it.
Don't work in the tutorial project THANKS :)
Get a good operating systems textbook.
Geez a beginner is no excuse for not learning at all.. You can search it easily in google..
OMG! You really want and should write down such novell for one easy thing? Seriously man You should do some more research - workarounds usually end up badly..
This is the most useless answer I have ever read on stackoverflow.
haha this one's still funny !!!
Which is interesting but doesn't actually answer the question.  See the accepted answer.
Moving along.....Please refrain from taking any jobs at nuclear power stations....
its a valit.. i don't need to worry about it.. and i want exact answer
Thanks for choosing an answer equals as mine which I posted 1 day earlier.
Maybe go wash that greasy finger.
congrats! you got a muppet upvote.
yeah right we can debug without a line of your code. what did you try where did you already searched ? we are not debuggers.
This question appears to be off-topic because it's a duplicate but I can't be arsed to search for it (much like the OP)
What the hell is `sub` anyways..?
Your use case is flawed. Reading a tag from the phone to which it is permanently attached is silly
I think your putting down votes for my all questions? Why? What's your problem?
I wonder why this answer is still showed up despite of the comment above.
go away!!!!!!!!!
this is a crappy question  what have you tried? is there something wrong with your code we won't know unless you show us?
Maybe you should learn Java before you try writing an Android app.
I've downvoted as you've had several responses and not replied to any of them.
I hope you are not a DBA
Sometimes I wanna shoot myself in the head.
What the hell is wrong with you ???? :D Seriously ? Comic Sans ???????
unclear is waaaaaaaaaaay too polite.  Flawed or crippled would be more like it.
It's a shame that someone doesn't know how to use keyboard shortcuts or how to read
how about doing a Google search. That's where you can ask. Everyone else has spent at least 30 minutes doing their own research first before asking questions.
If someone is experiencing this problem and using CocoaPods this is likely the correct solution.
Taught to do it this way at uni... Apparently it's bad jew jew haha
Why am i getting down votes.. i'm just asking a question... Dumb idiots some ppl r
how to solve it with C# - by writing some...
Want to -1 that shit-tier code style in that last comment but sadly (or luckily for you) stackoverflow doesn't have such a feature.
The person who down voted and marked as close if you're a man enough explain why you did it so we all know otherwise we all know what you're!!!
........go away
A thoroughly pointless question. If it did come before you would be asking why it didn't come after.
Don't worry about it. No one cares about your code
It wastes my time to try this solution.
because it is about reading comprehension.
OP clearly has no clue how to handle/manipulate and array
how about reading some documentation before posting such questions?
+1 RTFM and a link to TFM
take a look to my answer perhaps you can use it in your code to avoid going your shoulder to scratch your ass :)
And it shows only the javadoc for the current function not the hovered over object too. Really bad answer.
Mormon programmers FTW
That's the most pathetic answer I have ever encountered in Stack Exchange.
StackOverflow is not a developer-finding service.
this should be selected worst answer
Have you tried this yourself? By the way it doesn't work.
So why don't you do your own homework instead of dumping it here?
wins this thread over the pompous jerk who told her she doesn't get it.
It's cool that jsoup is smart enough to autocorrect your misspelling of chidl!
Patronising _and_ wrong. Nice.
Was writing this question easier than pressing enter? :)
Thanks for sharing your experience. But please try to focus on the relevant parts in future answers not telling everybody the story of your life..
lol very mature. My not knowing the np.nanmean command must made your miserable day
JFC! You must have _really_ good drugs
This is stupid. An implementing class should be able to choose what to expose outwards while providing internal functionality of the interface.
The link seems to not present any information at all ... Please do not troll if you are ...
Add explanation or don't post answers to such questions.
i am not at all interested in your meaning less crt baby reasons. some one as you with no morals and common sense make my blood boil
:sex <-- And this is a sex symbol!
man enough is enough i m not telling bad i m just saying you are annoying more than a 2 year old baby
Why does this question get so many upvotes when it it considered off-topic for this site (request for external resource).
The worst answer ever!
No exception -- the guy is just fishing for reputation points by posting bad questions and immediately self-answering them.
Which WebBrowser are you referring to in the code? The OP asked about WPF WebBrowser. Please stop fooling people.
So what did you ask? answers?
Uuuuuuuuuuuugggghhh.
Seriously did not even try did you. Please at least search Google if not stack overflow before posting a question.
What is the question. The forum is for english speakers ;)
doesn't work......stupid solution
Did anyone else but me /facepalm after reading this answer?
It could also clean your house cook some food and do all your work for you. That's a possibility.
*****: Do yourself and everyone else a favor and use ui-router.
Hahaha this is f****** absurd :D!
Screw you to the guy who voted down. No research effort? Really? For someone new to Linux getting as far as I did most certainly took a look of research effort.
Your teacher really does let you work with CI still...? That men must be like 80 years old?
We're not here to do your work for you...
Reading comprehension fail.
This is just wrong. Why would anybody upvote that?
I'll do it in a few minutes thanks for your advice.
Anyone have any idea why has to be an ass about it?  I came here to find the answer so it must not be THAT crazy to post it on SO loser.
Cogratulation. This is your second downwoted question today. Keep up! :)
The only possible explanation is that you are a terrible person and regularly beat small dogs just for fun.
Who made me downvote you're really damn idiot!!!
Yes very Annoying every time I post a question comment or reply comes much later but down voting comes first I think there are some fools who has only work of down voting
I always upvote a question that elicits a good answer no matter how dumb. +1 for you.
that code is a mess!!
Thats works like a cunt when you are also doing Django pagination!
Format your code properly first. It looks ugly.
This forum is about problem solving not dodging
`<pre><a href=<br />>Hey</pre>` and you're fucked. You better use html5lib to parse your HTML and modify your DOM.
if you werent such a knob you'd have given a worthwhile answer.
No one cares what is freaky or annoying. Just ask the question and skip the gratuitous emoting please.
Ok you cannot bother.
Man I fucked the editting of this post it's supposed to be http.post either way none of the calls work anymore and they did before.
Well it works in iphone / ipad size but now the fullscreen is fucked because it is no longer at the bottom of the page but instead of the content.
What's the point of digging up this questions ? If not for a boost of reputation ?? The OP goes back in 2011...
I don't see how this passed as a question back in 2012.  RTFM
dafuck? That's the most important part. The rest is useless without it.
That's retarded. I would never have thought of having to enter those other positional args before I could view help for a subcommand.
Android Studio sucks install IntelliJ. I have spent so many time with Android Studio some AH is managing this project at Google.
Haha ... removed your comment huh ? well i guess we all know who's right then...
My other aliases especially my favorite `alias fuck='sudo $(history -p \!\!)'`  show up though!
Fuck... Info... I think not works... Why what do you see? What is the error? Do not work... How to help if you say just that?
i will kill you!!!
you black dog where is your face huh?
this works but looks awful :D
libwebsockets is shit!!!
Fuck im completely stupid man.. I had a huge range. I should use offset for the list so to add on line for every new line.. Thanks a lot..
Man shut up ****.
Goddamnit. This is hopeless.
When I ask you a question what I need is an answer. Not two more questions.
Is Google not installed on your machine?
You're too sensitive to live.
I have upvoted your contribution in order to engage and to award your stupidity.
Answering and asking for more..
I honestly think you are just trolling me at this point. Good luck with your problem I hope you find a solution.
It's not that bad but yeah... I've seen prettier girls.
Fuck both of those things.  
Where is the spelling mistake? And again revert the formatting I dont want to keep manually undoing your mistakes. I dont want to have to ask you again.
liar! this doesn't work
StackOverflow: The correct answer is there but the prick who makes the most fun of the question no matter how incorrectly gets the most votes.
Oh dear you don't want to have it so complicated do you?
What have you tried so far? Did you do any research on the topic yourself?
attempt your assignment you lazy person!
utter rubbish.....
Study Basics...start with WPF-MVVM
lol read a book
I'm flagging this as a duplicate of this question; please don't cry
Note: if your C header `#include`s any `std*.h` headers you're fucked
That wasn't the question. But it's easy enough for anyone to figure out and if they can't then perhaps they shouldn't be coding.
If everything is synchronized why the fuck even care to do threads? -- My Old School Master
yup  i forgot to undo some change to another script and basically fucked myself over  i didn't find my solution but atleast i found my error  thx .
write some code. also congrats on the muppet upvote. dodgy as.
I got the same fucking issue like this: after a day coding a REST API file then save then re-open Eclipse again all my changes go away.
If you have to ask this you're not fit for the job sorry.
.equals() does the trick! fuck yeay stackoverflow is the shit!!! :D :D :D
Reason for the downvote coward!?
down vote for no explanation - i don't like magic here like  orig and other similarly
You are the problem with the online support community.
Don't ask a second question create a new question or better yet Google it!
Since you a being a grammar nazi you should have spotted the `if you doesn't`