Uhmm then something else i fucking it up - with .submit() - it's not working at all. Neither in chrome or firefox.
You can't. I just call my forced div `<div id=fuck-react>`.
You can't fool me - that's a JPEG and it doesn't have any transparent pixels.
Okay error gone! Got the html being dumped in via the file_get_contents now the scraper is fucked however you have been a great help so far!
Same answer as **** one just worse...
IMO git rm should just remove the file(s) from the git repo not the filesystem...so so stupid
i did this allready. I even tried to copy& paste some examples from the Jquery API into a text document on my computer AND EVEN those don't seem to work!?!? what the fuck
It does help. You are just lazy to use it in your openquery.
You tha real MVP
That's not going to happen.  [Read this](http://meta.stackexchange.com/questions/66377/what-is-the-xy-problem).
Do you have a variable `sc` defined at all?
What has this to do with the question? Are you astroturfing?
Looks like your cmd.exe comand is fucked up does Win+R -> cmd.exe work?
what the hell is this code?? where is the func of OutageViewModel.Id()? or   AfterSavedAll()??
what you said was so inspirational in 2009 such a shame  you didn't dig it further otherwise node js could be yours
WT? does not work did you tested?
your moms a terrible mess pal...................................
Your swift code is not pretty…
The one who downvoted me please don't be a kid. If you don't understand the question just tell me in a kind way. I don't like stupid people.
Thank you for helping me. I AM NEW TO PROGRAMMING and I simply wanted an answer. Now I know that this site does have a******* who are not very understanding individuals
...so wtf is then going on?
the one who downvoted me I cannot find any word to say to you. Dictionaries are not enough to describe the title for you.
My problem is in my code i wrote 2000 lines working with argv like char and now if i put it tchar my whole programm is fucked up...
:) always there is someone who gets negative votes even when everyone is getting a positive point.
got to love people who provide the laziest permanent fix ever
I don't see any code. Did you bother trying to google it on your own? Because I literally googled `java string replace after index` and it returned 800000 results
I tried posting my Logcat but it keeps saying there's a formatting problem. I spent about 20 minutes fucking around with it. I gave up.
Lol The JLS uses iff?
welcome to the internet.
This is not Instagram help desk.
i don't know why eitherjust did.. - best logic ever. I predict you'll have a long and successful programming career.
You posted a lot of unnecessary irrelevant HTML.
Could you also provide a pure Javascript solution?
holy fuck it all works now!
*I'm too low status to rep you it seems:(
Oh fucking crist! I can put an IF inside another IF? Thanks <3 Jesus bless you brah!
Someone is in a shitty downvote mood today without explaining the reason for the downvotes...
please question related answer not .. other.
unfucking believable!!!!! i was using fragments so I needed to add the dummy surfaceview to the main layout. thank you!!!
Checked POM contains single version of Spring Framework and <tx:annotation-driven /> is also there.
Seriously bro? do you even java?
This post is hilarious.
Removing the code has made your already obscure question completely meaningless.
Crap. Idiots ...
There are a lot of books with such kind of OOP bullshit. But why developers do such poor design of their systems (OOP design  too) using all this theoretical stuff?
Wow. I'm fucking stupid. Thanks **** it's been a long day!
Your question doesn't even make sense. Please try to write in a somewhat decent English.
**This is not a duplicate of How to compare Strings** Read the question properly before marking it.
Thank you so much 50 variable checks later I found out it had null because I fucked up in another place in the code .
Lol copy paste my answer
Yeah its obvious until I get the commenting privilege I will post answers the way I want.
Thanks. The `box-shadow` provided by bootstrap fuck this up. The issue was solved after override the `box-shadow` to `none`
if you use directive to set default value then may god blast me .
Did you tried anything ? SO is not a free code service we're happy to help on code with problems not doing your work/homework for free.
It's a copy and paste of my answer..
This has to be the most ridiculous way of going about solving the problem.
Apparently you need to add some booty pictures to change your downvotes to upvotes.
Ha. I mentioned it because your solution didn't use LEFT JOINS. Don't pretend otherwise! Also will your DISTINCT also count NULLS?
search on google .
Use your mind...Don't ask this type of silly question.
If you cant understand the question than get the hell out of here.
You're using the TTS in a very weird way.
You don't know enough SQL to create a `SELECT` query?
If this answered your question please accept it.
Happy new Year CYA!!!
Imo the google result fetching request and terrible question all together is more offensive than the word fucking. -1 nonetheless
If this solved your problem you might consider accepting this answer.
hahaha jsperf you fickle bitch... http://jsperf.com/periodicstrings/3
he said he wanted simple i gave him an approach what is your dysfunction?
Common sense!!!
I'm about 90% sure you're the same person as the one who asked the question.
non of your business. are you english teacher?
It does fucking compile -.- This is not the whole fucking code listen retard...
You found the documentation... did you read it? What's not clear?
Thank you **** however if you not prepared to help keep your stupid comments to yourself.
again mind your own business and stop bothering me.  if you don't want assist then stop wasting space on the site with your comments.
Did you try anything at all? Did you search for this? Do you even *know* JavaScript?
No this is stupid. Not even close to a generic solution. It could easily be dangerous.
Err... [RTFM](http://php.net/manual/en/function.preg-grep.php) maybe? Use `PREG_GREP_INVERT` as the 3rd parameter.
Which book are you using to learn C++?
you may want to check the stfu i aint politically correct policy. Oh wait it doesn't exist since it's given by nature.
I DONT GIVE A SHIT WRITE PROPER WORKING PRODUCT
What's the _question_? Just ask it and stop please. This is SO not your blog.
Didn't you already ask this question  twice before?
You have to create your own `WhatsApp` First
Are you trying to answer the question or be a smart ass? Really I can't tell by your comment.
What the fuck do you think I'm doing here asshole!? Research. Jesus christ! Why does the world have to include schmucks like you!? BTW happy new year
fuck everyone who downvotes
How would providing any code here help? Instead of being a code monkey how about look at what the issue is - that is what it means to be a computer scientist.
Im also voting to fuck off my post
because he is frustrated trolling in first day of new year
I'm voting to close this question as off-topic because it follows the pattern *<false statements> - Assuming this is true why is it in common use?*
Are you retarded?
http://blog.codinghorror.com/the-first-rule-of-programming-its-always-your-fault/
No error no excepted resualt i'm fucked up :)
Seriously ? It's the easiest programming task I've ever seen. Juste read some doc/tutorial about arrays
He's asking how to set an element in an array what do you think he has done so far ? Nothing.
Please answer as soon as you can because I would like to finish and work on other things.
Just because two languages start with the same letter does not mean they are the same.
next question will be I dug a hole and want to fall in tell me how
Take it to the psychiatrist.
yes N0b to sql ! u didnt help much lol
This should be the accepted answer not some xor crap.
You look so confused.
no.i just want to decode this shit
**** I haven't told you a code transtation service.if you know then answer if don't then skip.
yes thank you anywans look if you can help me not telling for stupid mistakes
Indeed not equals is the non-idiotic way of coding a relational exclusive or.
This is not a spoon feeding service! Show some code and learn [How to ask a good question](http://stackoverflow.com/help/how-to-ask)
F*cking hell this is actually a good question. What SE site should it go to so it doesn't get downvoted to oblivion?
People are helping you for FREE you ungrateful little shit.. be respectful and follow the rules and people will help you..
You mad? It is the same thing that my code contains.
then up vote :( :) bitches
You think I didn't? And the duplicate post does not contain the answer for my question.
you two guys want to suck my dildo?
fuck off **** asshole
I m going to fuck your mother **** fucker
fuck off **** fucker sucker
su.. my di.. ****
Im gonna fu.. your mother
Well try something. This isn't letuswriteyourcodeforyou.com .
Oh come on DataTable seriously?
I've been telling it trillions of times on this site. Searching shouldn't be hard. There's a textbox on the upper right corner that could be used for this purpose.
Huh?...........
This looks like ***guess work answer***.
Wtf is a dynamic pointer? Read a basic textbook
It still won't compile. You can find a lot of Articles & Tutorials related to Recursion in the Internet. I am afraid SO is not the place to ask such generic questions.
This answer is wrong. I have this problem in 2.48. Giving nonsense answers you will not gain reputation on Stackoverflow.
Found a workaround that doesn't seem to fuck up the rest of my program and does the job. Although I guess your way is still the correct way to approach this issue.
Thanks in advance.
Who uses the G-WAN web server? The G-WAN website and that's about it.
You seriously don't even know how to write code? **Kindly check out the [tour].**
Pop it in the oven on 200 for around 15 minutes
Who is the IMBECILE who deleted all the comments to this question???
skip learning if you don't like it (and stop wasting our time).
Questions asking us to recommend a technique or find a book tool software library tutorial or other off-site resource are off-topic for Stack Overflow
Don't be a dick about it. C++ provides you plenty of ways of working with ostensibly unrelated objects: see std::min. My question is reasonable. This answer isn't.
There are a sure load of prats on this site.
I assume you later on want to ask is lamborghini a vehicle?
And this does not do that?    You are beyond helping and I will remember to not try in the future.
I suggest looking at any of the thousands of calculator app examples out there. Have you even bothered trying to debug your code?
So you want us to google search for you now as well? Anything else you need? A sandwich? Some coffee?
`steam music android java` guess what happens when you google that? How stupid/lazy are you?
Real life must be a shocker if you think this is rude...
Sure in stackoverflow I really didn't understand why so many people post answers or downvote without a basic understanding of questions. lol
I have an easy suggestion: teach your developers your environment.
Yeah sure couple of SO users are already working on writing this code for you should be delivered soon ;)
you want fries with that?
what is this suX ?
if you had learned it you would have posted an answer ... so go learn it you too
SO isn't a free tutorial / guide service
hot. I mean the question this is interesting.
Looks like you lack basic OOP knowledge. I'm afraid you can't get help from here.
For saving image path first I've to upload the image right and then only i get image path to save into the table. wtf does that mean?
Try googling resize runtime winforms or change name to ilietopeople. Really.
vote or die madafaka
or you could just contribute to the community and mark **** answer. Credit the poeple that help you don't just turn around and start deleting shit..
why are you so vicious?
...and I want a cookie.Thanks for letting us know what you *want*.  What's your *question* though? What have you tried?
And I still want a cookie. I'd still like to know what your question is and what you've tried.
So give us a url then so we can see this not working.
Sure we'll just whip up something so you can spam your garbage app... Would you like a snack while you're waiting? Something poisonous perhaps?
I will get it I am determinated ;) so stop your stupid comment and just click - reputation ;)
lol. can't believe this answer gets 3 votes. must be all from your accounts. lol.
Could you be any more lazy?
Learn how to program before attempting anything as complex as a multi button GUI.
If you don't know the answer keep your mouth shut
Why you cannot use `each_with_index` ? Its some kind of homowork ?
thx for the downvote smuck
Google try and then ask questions.
Yeah well fuck your mother you retarded autist you should kill yourself you fucking skinny ass nazi.
lol fuck you puppy youre an ugly nazi anyway you fucking clown nerd ass bitch.
Lol you're probably a nazi anyway that's why you won't help a good jew like me.
Strictly speaking I'm an ugly nazi clown nerd ass bitch who knows the answer to this question.
Yeah you got that right you fucking nazi clown nerd ass bitch. Get a life maybe the only way you know the answer to this is if you have no life.
Screw you **** I already know your full name and I will not take measures to ruin your fucking life. Find it in your heart to hide yourself.
Thanks **** for another RELEVANT answer.
no need to be such assholes
Nope not at all. Check my answer I did it on my own.. No need for any of your comments telling me to combine all your posted pages which is ridiculous BTW.
Please capitalise punctuate and paragraph this mess.
Heh... :D Then what are you offering for me to do sir ****?
What a nice person have a good weekend :)
I have to stop SQL Reporting Services because dumbass Apache can't figure it's crap out on its own.  Why does open source stuff have to suck so much ass?
Sorry “change your platform” is shit advice.
lol i tried that yesterday and still doesn't work the way i want thanks for coming out as a brick though next time maybe don't try to help someone in need a-hole
I want a textview inside a relataive layout or any layout read the question first before answering dumbass
complete garbage
because `var ls = fs.readdir(process.argv[2]);` is undefined how the hell can we know why
whoa what the fuck guys all im saying is dont use a dot at the end only commas and semicolon are you guys fucking autistic?
sorry i cannot post more character over here. If you  have time  can you please look at the line from 365 - 413 .
and clean my room wash my car and do my laundry...
kya le ke aaye the kya le ke jauo ge comment main dala hota :D
Well sucks to be you then :)
yeah stupid analogy you do things better than me blah blah blah. Go ahead talk with them smartass : ****
fuck you son of a bitch
I'm not sure we can help you with mental health issues ?
holy shit thanks I found out that I had a row with 5 columns instead of 4
You are a fucking legend. Thank you so much!
Is google down?