Of course it's code you insensitive clod!
If you think you're being clever you aren't.
Mexican police takes a random african animal and pour soda with chili into its nose until it admits that it's an elephant.
Seriously? Did you even bother to look at the documentation for UIButton?
Just remember that they hate you
I like the obfuscation in your answer text.  Makes it very hard to read.  Ever heard of the Enter key?
You must live in a box then.
Yeah im a baby give it to me in a bottle lol.
I think we've reached a new low of laziness.
They are proud of it but sometimes it becomes pain in the ass.
Your answer on the other hand is worthless.
the curly quotes fsck with the code parsing
Your syntax is junk
I second the beatings.
Don't waste your time trying to make this work it isn't worth it.
This is pretty fec-ked up.  
Why on Earth would you want to imitate something this butt-ugly?
I would upvote this answer but I just hate this oh downvote me you senseless clods bullshit.  Especially repeated twice.
shut up sir.....
Its called your brain. If you can't competently review code ask someone else to do it.
goddamnit Novice is not the word
Your professor's a retard.  Not that strange really.
Haha what a retard yeah if I tried to build then I would have realized that :)
Stupid solution he's don't need that
Maybe b/c people like you that don't make useful feedback are the reason...
Everyone who thinks he can wiggle around writing a real parser by applying regex instead needs his nose wiped in the shit this inevitably ends in.
With a reputation > 7000 you might know where the Python documentation is.
omfg what is that?
Is this a troll?
look can you please stop posting such unrelated rubbish.
shut up............
Wow what a terrible mess.
Its the number of fucks will not reduce the gestation period
If somebody asked me that question I would want to punch them in the face. And then answer Apples and oranges
wtf? how is this a real question?
Have you bothered to actually look at the PHP docs and see how to do it or do you just want somebody to spoonfeed you the codez
blog post my foot.
wow now that is lazy... I can't believe people are actually willing to help you? :S
you improbably thorough m*****f****r.
Cant believe those Aholes -1 repped me
Is this homework?
hypercrypt it is a client's requirement.Client is female and she hates all the URL and website address stuff. :)
If API documents are hard for you to read then you should *learn* how to read them first.
And the award goes to the Asp.net team for most retarded class name...
witch! burn him!!
my eyes!!!!.............
Don't post question for silly mistakes.
You're an idiot.
R u crazy ****??I will give you -1 for this stupid answer.I am not asking for this.Please read my question carefully...
nut-searing pain - couldn't have said it better.
Try to switch on the thing between ya ears before spamming and make people waste their time.
can u figure out how to do this stupid crap?
Ask all those people who you've always heard this from.
It was the first result on the exact title as mentioned in the comment. Now it isn't. The first hit is now tragically this stupid question.
What a crazy idea to close this question! Jesus holy Chirst!
Bloody fool people don't try to give down vote without knowing the answers.. Give Down vote with justification.
just wtf... closevote
Thanks for time wasting.
OMG! You really want and should write down such novell for one easy thing? Seriously man You should do some more research - workarounds usually end up badly..
This is the most useless answer I have ever read on stackoverflow.
Maybe go wash that greasy finger.
congrats! you got a muppet upvote.
This question appears to be off-topic because it's a duplicate but I can't be arsed to search for it (much like the OP)
I think your putting down votes for my all questions? Why? What's your problem?
go away!!!!!!!!!
this is a crappy question  what have you tried? is there something wrong with your code we won't know unless you show us?
I hope you are not a DBA
Sometimes I wanna shoot myself in the head.
unclear is waaaaaaaaaaay too polite.  Flawed or crippled would be more like it.
It's a shame that someone doesn't know how to use keyboard shortcuts or how to read
Why am i getting down votes.. i'm just asking a question... Dumb idiots some ppl r
Want to -1 that shit-tier code style in that last comment but sadly (or luckily for you) stackoverflow doesn't have such a feature.
The person who down voted and marked as close if you're a man enough explain why you did it so we all know otherwise we all know what you're!!!
........go away
A thoroughly pointless question. If it did come before you would be asking why it didn't come after.
Don't worry about it. No one cares about your code
It wastes my time to try this solution.
Mormon programmers FTW
That's the most pathetic answer I have ever encountered in Stack Exchange.
this should be selected worst answer
wins this thread over the pompous jerk who told her she doesn't get it.
It's cool that jsoup is smart enough to autocorrect your misspelling of chidl!
lol very mature. My not knowing the np.nanmean command must made your miserable day
JFC! You must have _really_ good drugs
The link seems to not present any information at all ... Please do not troll if you are ...
i am not at all interested in your meaning less crt baby reasons. some one as you with no morals and common sense make my blood boil
:sex <-- And this is a sex symbol!
man enough is enough i m not telling bad i m just saying you are annoying more than a 2 year old baby
Why does this question get so many upvotes when it it considered off-topic for this site (request for external resource).
The worst answer ever!
No exception -- the guy is just fishing for reputation points by posting bad questions and immediately self-answering them.
doesn't work......stupid solution
Did anyone else but me /facepalm after reading this answer?
Screw you to the guy who voted down. No research effort? Really? For someone new to Linux getting as far as I did most certainly took a look of research effort.
Your teacher really does let you work with CI still...? That men must be like 80 years old?
Reading comprehension fail.
Anyone have any idea why has to be an ass about it?  I came here to find the answer so it must not be THAT crazy to post it on SO loser.
The only possible explanation is that you are a terrible person and regularly beat small dogs just for fun.
Who made me downvote you're really damn idiot!!!
Yes very Annoying every time I post a question comment or reply comes much later but down voting comes first I think there are some fools who has only work of down voting
that code is a mess!!
Thats works like a cunt when you are also doing Django pagination!
if you werent such a knob you'd have given a worthwhile answer.
Android Studio sucks install IntelliJ. I have spent so many time with Android Studio some AH is managing this project at Google.
Fuck... Info... I think not works... Why what do you see? What is the error? Do not work... How to help if you say just that?
i will kill you!!!
you black dog where is your face huh?
libwebsockets is shit!!!
Man shut up ****.
Goddamnit. This is hopeless.
You're too sensitive to live.
I have upvoted your contribution in order to engage and to award your stupidity.
I honestly think you are just trolling me at this point. Good luck with your problem I hope you find a solution.
It's not that bad but yeah... I've seen prettier girls.
Fuck both of those things.  
StackOverflow: The correct answer is there but the prick who makes the most fun of the question no matter how incorrectly gets the most votes.
attempt your assignment you lazy person!
utter rubbish.....
Study Basics...start with WPF-MVVM
lol read a book
I'm flagging this as a duplicate of this question; please don't cry
That wasn't the question. But it's easy enough for anyone to figure out and if they can't then perhaps they shouldn't be coding.
write some code. also congrats on the muppet upvote. dodgy as.
If you have to ask this you're not fit for the job sorry.
Reason for the downvote coward!?
down vote for no explanation - i don't like magic here like  orig and other similarly
You are the problem with the online support community.
Since you a being a grammar nazi you should have spotted the `if you doesn't`