If you think you're being clever you aren't.
Mexican police takes a random african animal and pour soda with chili into its nose until it admits that it's an elephant.
Just remember that they hate you
I think we've reached a new low of laziness.
They are proud of it but sometimes it becomes pain in the ass.
Your answer on the other hand is worthless.
Your syntax is junk
Don't waste your time trying to make this work it isn't worth it.
This is pretty fec-ked up.  
Why on Earth would you want to imitate something this butt-ugly?
shut up sir.....
Its called your brain. If you can't competently review code ask someone else to do it.
Your professor's a retard.  Not that strange really.
Maybe b/c people like you that don't make useful feedback are the reason...
Everyone who thinks he can wiggle around writing a real parser by applying regex instead needs his nose wiped in the shit this inevitably ends in.
With a reputation > 7000 you might know where the Python documentation is.
omfg what is that?
Is this a troll?
look can you please stop posting such unrelated rubbish.
shut up............
Wow what a terrible mess.
Its the number of fucks will not reduce the gestation period
If somebody asked me that question I would want to punch them in the face. And then answer Apples and oranges
wtf? how is this a real question?
Have you bothered to actually look at the PHP docs and see how to do it or do you just want somebody to spoonfeed you the codez
blog post my foot.
wow now that is lazy... I can't believe people are actually willing to help you? :S
you improbably thorough m*****f****r.
Cant believe those Aholes -1 repped me
And the award goes to the Asp.net team for most retarded class name...
witch! burn him!!
my eyes!!!!.............
Don't post question for silly mistakes.
You're an idiot.
R u crazy ****??I will give you -1 for this stupid answer.I am not asking for this.Please read my question carefully...
nut-searing pain - couldn't have said it better.
Try to switch on the thing between ya ears before spamming and make people waste their time.
can u figure out how to do this stupid crap?
Ask all those people who you've always heard this from.
It was the first result on the exact title as mentioned in the comment. Now it isn't. The first hit is now tragically this stupid question.
Bloody fool people don't try to give down vote without knowing the answers.. Give Down vote with justification.
just wtf... closevote
Thanks for time wasting.
This is the most useless answer I have ever read on stackoverflow.
Maybe go wash that greasy finger.
This question appears to be off-topic because it's a duplicate but I can't be arsed to search for it (much like the OP)
go away!!!!!!!!!
this is a crappy question  what have you tried? is there something wrong with your code we won't know unless you show us?
Sometimes I wanna shoot myself in the head.
unclear is waaaaaaaaaaay too polite.  Flawed or crippled would be more like it.
It's a shame that someone doesn't know how to use keyboard shortcuts or how to read
Why am i getting down votes.. i'm just asking a question... Dumb idiots some ppl r
Want to -1 that shit-tier code style in that last comment but sadly (or luckily for you) stackoverflow doesn't have such a feature.
The person who down voted and marked as close if you're a man enough explain why you did it so we all know otherwise we all know what you're!!!
........go away
A thoroughly pointless question. If it did come before you would be asking why it didn't come after.
Don't worry about it. No one cares about your code
Mormon programmers FTW
That's the most pathetic answer I have ever encountered in Stack Exchange.
this should be selected worst answer
wins this thread over the pompous jerk who told her she doesn't get it.
lol very mature. My not knowing the np.nanmean command must made your miserable day
The link seems to not present any information at all ... Please do not troll if you are ...
i am not at all interested in your meaning less crt baby reasons. some one as you with no morals and common sense make my blood boil
:sex <-- And this is a sex symbol!
man enough is enough i m not telling bad i m just saying you are annoying more than a 2 year old baby
The worst answer ever!
doesn't work......stupid solution
Did anyone else but me /facepalm after reading this answer?
Screw you to the guy who voted down. No research effort? Really? For someone new to Linux getting as far as I did most certainly took a look of research effort.
Anyone have any idea why has to be an ass about it?  I came here to find the answer so it must not be THAT crazy to post it on SO loser.
The only possible explanation is that you are a terrible person and regularly beat small dogs just for fun.
Who made me downvote you're really damn idiot!!!
Yes very Annoying every time I post a question comment or reply comes much later but down voting comes first I think there are some fools who has only work of down voting
Thats works like a cunt when you are also doing Django pagination!
if you werent such a knob you'd have given a worthwhile answer.
Fuck... Info... I think not works... Why what do you see? What is the error? Do not work... How to help if you say just that?
i will kill you!!!
you black dog where is your face huh?
Man shut up.
You're too sensitive to live.
Fuck both of those things.  
StackOverflow: The correct answer is there but the prick who makes the most fun of the question no matter how incorrectly gets the most votes.
attempt your assignment you lazy person!
utter rubbish.....
Study Basics...start with WPF-MVVM
lol read a book
That wasn't the question. But it's easy enough for anyone to figure out and if they can't then perhaps they shouldn't be coding.
write some code. also congrats on the muppet upvote. dodgy as.
If you have to ask this you're not fit for the job sorry.
Reason for the downvote coward!?
down vote for no explanation - i don't like magic here like  orig and other similarly
You are the problem with the online support community.
Since you a being a grammar nazi you should have spotted the `if you doesn't`
Pure science? WTF does that mean? You think NaCl doesn't come in a 1:1 relationship?
Use your mind...Don't ask this type of silly question.
This shows remarkably little effort.
man this is a programming forum not trig.
WTH? TIA? This Is Awkward? Typical Ignorant American?
got to love people who provide the laziest permanent fix ever
again mind your own business and stop bothering me.  if you don't want assist then stop wasting space on the site with your comments.
This is stupid. An implementing class should be able to choose what to expose outwards while providing internal functionality of the interface.
I don't see how this passed as a question back in 2012.  RTFM
-1 useless answer
Okay this one gets my funniest post of the day.  :)
And maybe taking a class on databases. Or even just reading all the way through a tutorial.
liar! this doesn't work
